Black people still sell their own people
today, too. By the way, I don't know if
I'm going to last.
>> We're selling our own people today. I
don't know if I'm going to last. You
probably won't last with me.
>> I won't because your ignorance is so
over.
>> That's liberal. Truth is um in my Amanda
Seal uh debate.
She was the worst
uh Jubilee
surprise guest probably that they had.
Uh she was the stereotypical black
woman. She was angry. She was nasty. Uh
she threatened to have people removed
off. Uh there was uh one uh black
conservative who's known who was removed
because he she yelled at people. Several
times she threatened about five or six
times. She was a diva. Uh six or seven
times she threatened to leave. Now I'm
thankful for the opportunity, thankful
for getting to sit down with her. I
respect her for what she's accomplished.
But as a person, I have no respect for
her. She was very disrespectful to me uh
because I believe I destroyed her in my
f to start off and she didn't want to
talk to me again. Um, and I wouldn't
want to talk to me because she can't
beat me in a debate.